odosta.com 2013-12-06

# Privacy Policy | -::Create Your Own Tech World::-

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for all pages and services offered by ODosta.com

**» Personally Provided Information  
**

You do not have to give us personal information to visit ODosta.com. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

**» Website Traffic Analysis Software  
**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

**» E-mail Newsletters**

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by FeedBurner, however we use in-house solution for weekly Newsletter. We/Feedburner use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

**Third Party Advertising Partners**

All users of ODosta must keep this in mind that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on ODosta.com.

For, instance one of our partners, Google uses the [ DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) on ODosta.com displaying AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats. ****

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them. ****  
**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.  
**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by ODosta is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of ODosta except for use as indicated above.   
**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.  
**How does ODosta use login information?**  
ODosta uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.  
**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at [info@odosta.com](mailto:info@odosta.com) ****  
**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. ****

**External Links**

Our web sites contain links to other sites. ODosta.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.

Note: This Page can get updated any time, without an prior noitce, So Check back Often.

Last updated: June 25, 2012

© 2012 **ODosta** , All rights reserved. 

Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials  
from this Site is expressly prohibited.
